Innocence will fall prey.
The Cursed is a horror, drama, thriller film directed by Sean Ellis.
In the late 19th century, a brutal land baron slaughters a Roma
clan, unleashing a curse on his family and village.
In the days that follow, the townspeople are plagued by nightmares, the
baron's son goes missing, and a boy is found murdered.
The locals suspect a wild animal, but a visiting pathologist warns
of a more sinister presence lurking in the woods.
John McBride, played by Boyd Holbrook.
Isabelle Laurent, played by Kelly Reilly.
Seamus Laurent, played by Alistair Petrie.
Anais, played by Roxane Duran.
Alfred Moliere, played by Nigel Betts.
Saul, played by Stuart Bowman.
The Cursed is a 2021 gothic horror film written,
directed and co-produced by Sean Ellis.
The film stars Boyd Holbrook, Kelly Reilly, Alistair Petrie, and Roxane Duran.
Its plot follows a 19th-century village in rural
France that is menaced by a werewolf.
An international co-production of the United States and France, The Cursed premiered
at the 2021 Sundance Film Festival under the title Eight for Silver.
It was released in the U.S.
on February 18, 2022, by LD Entertainment.
It received generally positive reviews from critics.
The film explores themes of gypsy, world war i, gore, flashback, werewolf.
The tone is intense and dark and emotional.